American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  January 1-6, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  January 7-9, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  January 10-13, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  January 14-16, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  January 17-18, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  January 19-22, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  January 23-25, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  January 26-31, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  February 1-4, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  February 5-7, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  February 8-13, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  February 14-18, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  February 19-20, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  February 21-27, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  February 28, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  March 1-5, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  March 6-9, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  March 10-11, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  March 12-13, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  March 14-18, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  March 19-22, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  March 24-27, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  March 28-31, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  April 1-3, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  April 4-5, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  April 7-9, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  April 10-13, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  April 14-18, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  April 19-21, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  April 22-30, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  May 1-9, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  May 10-17, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  May 19-22, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  May 23-27, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  May 28-31, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  June 1-7, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  June 8-15, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  June 16-18, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  June 19-24, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  June 25-27, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  June 28-30, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  July 1-2, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  July 3-6, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  July 7-9, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  July 10-13, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  July 15-18, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  July 19-27, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  July 28-31, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  August 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  September 1930
- September 1930 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  October 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  November 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  December 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  December 15, 1930
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  January 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 56)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 58)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 59)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 60)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 61)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 62)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 63)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 64)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 65)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  February 1-2, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  February 3, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  February 4-5, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  February 6-7, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  February 8-9, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  February 10, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  February 11, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  February 12-15, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  February 16, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  February 17-18, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  February 19-25, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  February 26-28, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  March 2-3, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  March 4-8, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  March 9-11, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  March 12-15, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  March 16-18, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  March 19-21, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  March 23-27, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  March 28-31, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  April 1-3, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  April 4-9, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  April 10-12, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  April 13-14, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  April 15-18, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  April 20-22, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  April 23-25, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  April 27-31, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  May 1-6, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  May 7-12, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  May 13-19, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  May 20-22, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  May 23-26, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  June 1-2, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  June 3, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  June 4-5, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  June 6-9, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  June 10-13, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  June 14-16, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  June 17-24, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  June 25-30, 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  July 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  August 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  September 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  October 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  November 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  December 1931
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 56)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  January 1-4, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  January 5, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  January 6-7, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  January 8-9, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  January 10-12, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  January 13-14, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  January 15-16, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  January 17-19, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  January 20-21, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  January 22, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  January 23-25, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  January 26, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  January 27, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  January 28-29, 31, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  February 1-2, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  February 3-4, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  February 5-6, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  February 7-9, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  February 10, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  February 11-12, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  February 13-15, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  February 16-17, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  February 18-19, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  February 20-22, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  February 23, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  February 24-25, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  February 26-27, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  February 28-29, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  March 1, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  March 2-3, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  March 4-5, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  March 6-7, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  March 8-9, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  March 10-11, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  March 12-14, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  March 15, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  March 16, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  March 17-18, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  March 19-21, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  March 22-23, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  March 24-27, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  March 28, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  March 29, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  March 30-31, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  April 1-2, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  April 3-4, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  April 5, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  April 6, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  April 7, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  April 8, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  April 9-11, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  April 12-13, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  April 14, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  April 15, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  April 16-18, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  April 19, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  April 20, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  April 21, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  April 22-25, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  April 26-28, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  April 29-31, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  May 1-4, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  May 5-6, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  May 7-10, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 65)
  May 11-14, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  May 15-18, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  May 19-20, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  May 21-24, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  May 25-28, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  May 29-31, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  June 1-2, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  June 3-5, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 73)
  June 6-8, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 74)
  June 9-11, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 75)
  June 13-15, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 76)
  June 16-18, 20, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 77)
  June 21-25, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 78)
  June 27-30, 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  July 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  August 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  September 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  October 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  November 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  December 1932
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 59)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 60)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  January 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 64)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 65)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 67)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 68)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 69)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 70)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 71)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 72)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 73)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 74)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  February 1-2, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  February 3-4, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  February 5-6, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  February 7-8, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  February 9, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  February 10-11, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  February 12-14, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  February 15-16, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  February 17, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  February 18-20, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  February 21-23, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  February 24, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  February 25-27, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  February 28, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  March 1-2, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  March 3-5, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  March 6-7, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  March 8-10, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  March 11-13, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  March 14-15, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  March 16, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  March 17-20, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  March 21-23, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  March 24-27, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  March 28-29, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  March 30-31, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  April 1-4, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  April 5-6, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  April 7-10, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  April 11-12, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  April 13-14, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  April 15-17, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  April 18, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  April 19-20, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  April 21-23, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  April 24-26, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  April 27-28, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  April 29-30, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  May 1-3, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  May 4-5, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  May 6-9, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  May 10-11, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  May 12-14, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  May 15-16, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  May 17-21, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  May 22-23, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  May 24-25, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  May 26-31, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  June 1-3, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  June 5-6, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  June 7-8, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  June 9-12, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  June 13-15, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  June 16-20, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  June 21-23, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  June 24-26, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  June 27-30, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  July 1-6, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  July 7-10, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  July 11-13, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  July 14-17, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  July 18-20, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  July 21-25, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  July 26-28, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  July 29-31, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  August 1-2, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  August 3-4, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  August 5-7, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  August 8-11, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  August 12-14, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  August 15-17, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  August 18-25, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  August 26-29, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  September 1-11, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  September 12-19, 1933
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  September 20-25, 1933